kanbanflow.com 2019-04-04

# KanbanFlow - Lean project management. Simplified.

When we refer to “CodeKick”, "we", "our" and "us" we mean CodeKick AB, the company behind this service. When we refer to "service" we mean the KanbanFlow service which includes, but is not limited to, this web application and API.

When we use "you" we mean any individual that signs up for this service, or, the legal entity the individual is authorized to represent. If you are accessing the service on behalf of your employer, you warrant that you have the authority to agree to these terms on its behalf.

## Personal data we collect and use

### Name and email

To create an account we need your name and email address. They can be visible to other members of boards and organizations that you are or have been member of. Your name and email are used to identify your user in support errands. If needed you can change both from **Account settings**.

If you are mentioned inside a comment and want that name to be changed or removed, you agree that you will direct that request to the board owner.

Your email will also be used to send you notifications and newsletters. Notifications and newsletters can be toggled from **Account settings > Configure notifications**.

### Uploaded images

You have the option to upload an avatar. The avatar can be visible to other members of boards and organizations that you are or have been member of. You can remove and change your avatar from **Account settings**.

### Billing information

When you sign up for a premium subscription your billing information is needed. You may update your billing information under **Subscription** in your organization settings.

### Location data

When you log in we automatically store your IP address so that you can identify and log out of other devices remotely. You can choose to log out of all or specific devices from **Account settings > View login sessions**.

We may also store your IP address in logs for security and debugging purposes. Those logs are automatically deleted on a regular basis.

## Managing your personal data

### Security

We take data security seriously and strive to follow best practices for securing your data. See Terms of Service for more information.

Some support requests may require access to your board or account. In most cases this is not necessary. Any information we see when helping you in the support request will not be disclosed by us to any external parties.

We may also require access to your account if we suspect that you are violating our terms by for example attempting to hack into the service or on purpose trying to overload or disrupt it.

### Deletion

Deleting your account is a permanent action that can delete all personal data related to your account. You may accept that we can keep your full name when you delete your account. This can be helpful for other users when for example you have written comments or made changes on their boards. If you do not accept, your full name will be replaced with an anonymous text. See **Storage** for exceptions.

### Storage

Normally, we will store your personal data no longer than 30 days after you delete your account. We may keep some of your information if necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to enforce our agreements or to support business operations.

### Portability

To have all your data that we store sent to you, send us a request by email to [portability@kanbanflow.com](mailto:portability@kanbanflow.com). We will respond with a link to download your data within two weeks.

## Third parties

We do not sell or trade your personal data to outside parties. We do share some data with service providers for processing payments, sending emails, storing data and hosting our main and backup services. All third parties we share personal data with are compliant with GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation).

We may release your information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property or safety.

### Attaching files

In our premium version, you can attach files from Google Drive, Dropbox and Box to your tasks. To support that, you will be asked to give read-only permission to the service you use. For a file attached from those services, we will store a link and metadata on our servers but not the actual file content.

## Cookies

Cookies are small files a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. They enable the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

You need to have cookies enabled to log in and use this service.

## Child policy

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 16 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 16 years old or older.

## Terms of Service

Please also read our Terms of Service establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our service.

## Your consent

By using our service, you consent to our Privacy Policy. You have the right to complain to the data protection authority in the country where you live, work or where you feel your rights were not upheld.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. For significant changes you will be prompted from the application and/or by email to accept those changes to keep using the service.

## Contact information

Your information is controlled by CodeKick. If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us on [info@kanbanflow.com](mailto:info@kanbanflow.com).
